Guide to the Lee Felsenstein Papers M1443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Golemics
  - Subseries 2.8: Business Records
    - Joaquin Miller, Lovelace Computing, Lloyds Bank, Taylor and Co., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Agreements, Patent Applications, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
    - Boot Up, Set Date (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Job 109-PC, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Upstart P.O.s to be typed, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Blank Golemics purchase request forms (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Purchasing Notes, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Golemics P.O.s to be typed, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Golemics vs. Breiner and Bodian, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Agreements, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - phone lists, references, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - sample shipping documents, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Moore Systems, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Internal Memos; Agreements, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - P.O.s and Other to be typed, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Equipment on Loan; includes handwritten contracts, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Golemics P.O. Reconcile, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Simon's board, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Unemployment, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Key Log-2600 Tenth Street, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Confidential Staff Personal Information forms (blank) (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Bourgien, John, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Felsenstein, Lee, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Simpson, John, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Waters, Aaron, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Milstead, Jeffrey K., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Malm, Elaina, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Video Modular Systems business, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - China Trade, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      includes hand-written letter from Chinese people about buying and using the Apple II
    - Legal Counsel, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Petty Cash, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous business records, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Funny Signs (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Invoices, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Invoices, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - HASCI (Human Applications Standard Computer Interface) article, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - LSI 11, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Furniture/Equipment Requests, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Ace, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Save Old Sols (SOS) sales orders, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Tools / Equipment, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - FP Controller Combo, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Agency Approvals, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - System Spec, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Proposal, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Clock / Calendar; includes a certificate for shares of Golemics stock, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Interface Logic / Timing, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Fabrication, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Assembly, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Block Diagram, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Test Procedure, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Theory of Operation-Rainbow Systems Board, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - List of Materials-Rainbow Systems Board, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Color/Monochrome Display Board, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Hard Disk System, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - System Generation Procedures, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Rainbow-Board, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - California Software Research, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Electro Review Catalog, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Hard Drive Controller, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Schematic, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Rainbow Hard Disk Controller Board-Theory of Operation, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Rainbow-List of Materials, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Rainbow-Compatibility Evaluation, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Schematics, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Schematic, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Rainbow-Contract with OKI, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Rainbow-Weekly Reports, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Rainbow-Technical, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Rainbow-Correspondence from OKI, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Rainbow-Aida, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Rainbow-Koami, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Rainbow-Ashida, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Rainbow-Project Management, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Rainbow - W. James, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - R. Chapman, R. Stauduhar, J. Reykjalin, J. Fosse, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Rainbow-schematics, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Mono Board-fabrication, assembly, materials list, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Color Display Board, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Rainbow-schematics, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Color Video Board-fabrication, assembly, materials list, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - 6845 model, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - System ROM, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Microsoft DOS 2.0-Bios, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Microsoft Graphics BASIC 2.0-Bios, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Flat Panel Display, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - FP Controller, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Combo Board-fabrication, assembly, materials list, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - System Box, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - System Specifications, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Rainbow-proposal, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Video Display Adapter-fabrication, assembly, materials list, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - System Board, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Schematics, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - 8088, 8087, 8086, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - IO Decoding, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - RAM, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - FDD Adapter765, SIO 8250, PPIO 8255, Clock/Cal 58321, System Clock 8284, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Memory-fabrication, assembly, materials list, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Rainbow-miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 42-44)
    - Unemployment, resignation / layoff notices, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Jeff Milstead correspondence, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Vendor information, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Job 111, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - PC and AT ROM sets, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Rainbow documents, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 50-51)
    - Rainbow theory of operation; computer manuals; schematics, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Schematics; correspondence, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Stuff available for OCC-01, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Propaganda Received and of Interest, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Light Pens-PC compatible, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Equipment Cost Information, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Materials Lists; Parts Count; Receipts fm #102, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Manufacturing Purchase Requisition-History Cards for: connectors, oscillators, switches, capacitors, resistors, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Manufacturing Purchase Requisition-History Cards for Chips, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Virtual Mouse, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - PASCAL source and original work notes, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Memos-A.W., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Lee's Original Sketches [schematics], 1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Doug's drawings and notes [schematics], 1985 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Extra Xeroxes [schematics], 1985 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Job 111 [schematics], 1985 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Requisition Forms, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Lists of Materials, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Job 105, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Easy Link, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - VM/CIS Equipment to be returned, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Insurance Company Brochures, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Industry Letter-general, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Client Prospects-notes and draft proposals, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Plexus Sales-leads and prospects, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Requests for Proposals, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Job 116 and 117 docs; patent for method and apparatus for digital image smoothing, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Job 116-plasma controller board, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Job 111-contract, documentation, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Job 112, 113, 114, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Britton Lee-SCSI to 802.5 design, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Britton Lee-proposal, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Britton Lee-general, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Job 110, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Job 109, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Job 108, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Job 106, 107, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Job 105-Ricoh, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Job 103, 104, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Job 102-proposals and preliminary specifications, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Job 102-proposals and preliminary specifications, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Job 102-copyright license, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Job 102-combo board, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Job 102-Hard Disk Controller-Theory of Operation, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Job 102-Equipment Specification DK503 Series Disk Drive, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Job 102-Switch Settings for the Memory Expansion Card, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Job 102-Clock / Calendar Operation, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Job 102-GW Basic materials, Compatibility Evaluation, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Job 102-Reports of Differences, Future Computing, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Job 102-Survey of IBM PC 10 Addresses, comment on ROM-BIOS, Timing Diagrams, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Job 102-Software Development report, PC Board status, Reykjalin's Answers to Software Questions, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Job 102-Software reports, list of deliverables, list of materials, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Job 102-receipts, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Job 102-parts inventories, invoices, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Job 102-equipment lists, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Job 102 - photos of Work In Progress: Slides, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Job 102-Technical References, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Job 102-MS DOS 2.0 Utiltiy Extensions, invoices, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Job 102-purchase orders, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Job 102-Use Licences and Agreements, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Job 102-bank wire transfer reports, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Job 102-OKI CMOS Gate Array design manual, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Job 101 (Mimi Shevitz), 1984 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - CSR+DP 82 Agreement - EXH A (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - R+D Agreement PS (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - CSR+D Administration, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - CSR+D Certificate of Ltd. Partnership, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Michael Rossman + CSR+DP (for July '83), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Option and Agreement for Sale of New Tech (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Option and Non Exclusive License (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - CSR+D (G>CS+D>PS) Notes Assigned (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Inventory (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - SOLS (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Inventory (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Alarm, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Development Projects, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Momentum-Trial Period Info + Notes, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Expander Info + Notes, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Kingfisher Systems, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Pacific Software, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Equip + Furn Lease Notes, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Pacific Sftwr - Bus. Plan, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - General Eclectic, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - LGC Form Letter to General Eclectics, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - PICA-Public Interest Computer Association, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Community Memory-Bernal Heights pilot (internal documents), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - California Sotware Research and Development-bank statements, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - California Sotware Research and Development-correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - 1736 94th Avenue-invoices paid, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Lee's Auto Loan, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Credit applications; paid bills, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Phone bills, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Taxes, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Phone labels, address labels, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Paid invoices, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Hall-Mark account, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Credit card accounts, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Shipping receipts, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Golemics bank statements, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Golemics bank statements, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - California First Bank-account set up, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Workman's Compensation, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - User manuals, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Cancelled checks, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - In-House Equipment, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Travel, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Digital Electronic Design vols. 1 and 2. Catt, Walton, Davidson (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Community Memory-articles, newsletters, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Articles re: hacking, Osborne downfall, misc, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, schematics, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Hardware - photos and instructions, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Expander Upgrade Board, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Big Sky Telegraph-University of Montana, Western Montana College, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Volunteer Centers-Alameda County, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Golemics Open Payables A-L, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Golemics Open Payables M-Z, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      contains 5-1/4 floppy disk
    - Technical Products-vendors' promotional literature, 1985 - 1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      contains 3-1/2 floppy disk
    - Lee Felsenstein's business card from GLAV-PC (a US-USSR joint software development venture), 1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Golemics-IBM compatible ROMBIOS program, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Golemics-business records, correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Virtual Mouse schematics, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Job 139, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Army, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Felsenstein's The Golemic Approach (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Compaq / Packard-Bell, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Digital Research-company information, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - 128200-construction, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Present (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Memos, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Plan (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Reddy Information Systems v. Lee Felsenstein, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Grey/Megots, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - EPD Lawsuit, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Show Cause, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Affidavit/TRO (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Reddy-Rubenstein, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Reddy Settlement/Agency (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Misc Memos Re: Reddy v. Felsenstein, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Liz Rich (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - 3.4 Supermouse, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - 4.3 Expansion Unit, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Video Signal Processor (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - RF PROC (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - US Patents (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Schematics and Specifications, 1984 - 1994 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Insurance Co-Op Lease Bus. Lic. Fict. Name (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Confidential Information (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Filo 233 Microcomputer Index, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - LF personal-Sequia Automobile Insurance (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - LF Application to take over GECC Auto Lease #L5504138 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Lee Felsenstein-Personal Charge Accts., Income Tax + Related (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - P.S. Lease Information, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - For Golemics P/S (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Signed Contracts w/ Contractors Originals (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - #114 Original, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Original Contract Job #112, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Original Contract Job #111, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Original 102 Signed Contract, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Orig. 102 Contract Amendment, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - #102 Combo BD Agreement unsigned as of 4/24/85 (work done pymt. rec'd), 1985 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - #104 Agreement/Proposal (No Formal Contract) (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - #105 Signed Contract, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Orig. Signed Sequitur Software Agreement PS/Golemics (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Osborne Computer Corporation stock transfers, 1982 - 1987 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Fax reports, 1984 - 1987 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Fax messages, 1984 - 1987 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Fax messages-Job 109, 110, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Fax messages-#102 client, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Fax messages, Mar. - Apr. 1984 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Fax messages, Jan. - Feb. 1984 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Fax messages, May - July 1984 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Fax messages #102 client, Nov. 1984 - Dec. 1985 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Fax messages-Fosse / HDC, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Fax messages, Aug. - Oct. 1984 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Fax messages-Yoshi's only, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - California Software Research and Development-audit related materials, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - California Software Research and Development-partnership, income tax returns, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Credit Reporting, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Dun and Bradstreet information, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Visa applications (blank) Japan, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Vendor and Credit information, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Established credit-also resale cards mailed, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Vendors: Chron., Corr., misc., 1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Industry Letters, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Apollo Computer, Inc., 1986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - AT&T-agreements and info, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Computer Media Directory, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Dialog Information Services, Inc., 1986 (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
    - Richard G. Grey-attorney at law, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - The Laser Edge, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Mentor Graphics-brochures and specifications, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Mentor Graphics-correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Mentor Graphics-service history file, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Mentor Graphics-license and maintenance agreements, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Mentor Graphics-George Morrow timesharing, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - MCI / SBS Skyline, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Geoffrey Hughes-OKI, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Ashida-OKI Electric, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Pacific Bell-phone service information, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Pacific Software-correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Ricoh, Inc.-market information, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Richfield Capital-Joe Castro, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Saul Zaentz Company, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Synergy Printer Systems-correspondence, maintenance agreements, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Easylink, Western Union data, Telex information, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - X.Dot Corporation-correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Accelerator and Memory Boards-information, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Advertising, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Possible Sources for Assembly Work, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Business and Marketing consultants, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Capitol Equipment data sheets, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Clerical (Temp) resources, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Diskettes and Duplication services, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Hardware and Software consultants, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Misc. Legal and Professional services, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - List services, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Office Space data sheets, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Printing and Paper Supply sources, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Search Companies, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Software Programs, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Resumes, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Resumes-Systems Design and Programming, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Lee Felsenstein's resume and cover letter, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Resumes-technical writing, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Log-Lee Felsenstein's resumes and cover letters sent, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Mini / Micro West-83 program-participation info; The Shakeout in Desktop and IBM compatibility, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Steve Ditlea Digital Deli, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - UC Berkeley Academic Computing Newsletter, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - New Improved Guide to the Hardware Filing Cabinets, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - IBM / PC software compatibility chart, articles, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Newsletter (Toronto, Canada) re: The VDT Blues, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Technical Articles, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Local Area Networks (LAN) data sheets, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Advanced Information Displays-Crystal Vision, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Newsletters: Subroutines, Soft Letter, Britton Lee: Ink, 1984 - 1987 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Dialog Chronolog [not a complete run], Aug. 1985 - Nov. 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Hacker's conference, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Kiplinger Letters, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
    - The Database Engine, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Slate Reunion, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Project Prometheus article by Lee Felsenstein - ROM Magazine, Nov. 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Lee Felsenstein talk at Computer Literacy, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Jake Felsenstein's Papers, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Samples of Layout/Fabrication/Stuffing of Boards (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Cities West (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Typeset Camera-Ready Copy Seq + Golemics (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Keys - 2608 8th 916 Parker (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Lou Katz (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - New Improved Guide to Hardware Filing Cabinets, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Leaseametrics, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Golemics Job # Log (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - J File (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - OKI Electric Letterhead Pg 1 + 2nd Pgs (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Nondisclosure Agreements --signed-- Originals, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Golemics Employee Time Sheets, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Golemics Employee Time Sheets P/R info, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Golemics Employee Individual Records, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Golemics Employee Time Sheets P/R info, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Sick/Vacation and Holiday-log, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Chris Helps Contract Notes (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Golemics Employee Time Sheets P/R info, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - PO Master File, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - PO Master File, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Payroll Ledgers, 1983 - 1984 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Unemployment Ins. Claims, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Work Sharing Unemployment Calif. EDD, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Unemployment Ins. Claims, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Closed Vendors (A-Z), 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Arrow Electronics-closed, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Cameragraphics, Electronics Etc., US Courier Corp.-closed, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Pacific Bell telephone account-paid bills, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Closed Vendors (A-Z), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Marshall, Mentor Graphics, Plexus Computers-closed, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Schwabacher/Frey, Q-Tronix/TVA, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - US Courier Corp.-closed, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Invoices and Statements to be checked/entered, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Golemics paid bills, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 17-18)
    - Various business cards, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Articles about Soviets and computer technology, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Index to file folders (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Newsletters and Mail, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Announcements, Newsletters, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Index to file folders, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 26)